Playtime is finished, the clock says tick-tock,
Time to gather up every wooden block!
Pencils in the cup,crayons in the box,
Pair up the teddy bear's cozy little socks!
Look on the table and look on the rug,
Give your messy room a big tidy hug!
Clean up, clean up, quick as you can!
Everyone can help, we have a great plan!
Pick it up, put it away,
Ready for another happy day!
Books on the bookshelf, standing in a row,
Where do all the shiny toy cars go? in the basket
one, two, three, Everything is neat as neat can be!
High five your buddy, high five your friend,
Now we reached our tidy finish end!
Clean up, clean up, quick as you can!
Everyone can help, we have a great plan!
Pick it up, put it away,
Ready for another happy day!
You are a superstar helper!
OH OH